REGAN O'BRIEN

Chicago, IL 60618 | Mobile (847) 814-0592 | regan.elaine36@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/regan-obrien

UX Designer/UX Researcher

USER-OBSESSED • DEEPLY CURIOUS • CREATIVE & PRAGMATIC

UX Designer who's customer obsessed and deeply curious. Design thinking, user research, prototyping, wireframing, affinity diagrams, and usability testing every day. Creating intuitive user experiences by challenging and committing. Converge together, diverge individually. Growth mindset all day; adaptable perseverance. Natural-born organizer and leader. My motto is "put me in, coach".

- Figma & Miro Software
- Constructive Feedback
- Prototyping & Wireframing
- User Research
- Slide Decks
- Cross Dept. Communication
- Journey Map & Storyboard
- Problem Solving
- Adaptability

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Non-Profit Office - Curriculum Specialist/Administrative Assistant

Wright Foundation for the Realization of Human Potential, Chicago, IL

2022-2023

- Generate on-brand, eye-catching, and thoughtful PowerPoint presentations by updating outlines with notes and cues, and editing content for presenters in order to have successful, engaging events.
- Collaborated with founders and speakers on curriculum by writing new material, and creating content that spoke to attendees for authentic, mission-driven speaking events.
- Automate outdated curriculum processes through analyzing and updating systems in order to improve efficiency for Admin team and the organization as a whole which resulted in more streamlined workflow and fewer errors.
- Write, edit, proofread, and distribute communications in order to provide engaging, clear and relevant content to the target audience.
- Plan and organize in-person events while managing deadlines and calendars, overseeing set-up, collaborating across departments, and supplying appropriate materials to ensure events run smoothly.
- Scheduling and email management for the organization's founder through field meeting requests, while ensuring the schedule was organized and that enough time was allocated for each event.

Coach - Fitness

Self-Employed & Gyms, Madison, WI & Chicago, IL

2017-2022

- Manage up to 35 clients weekly through daily schedule coordination in order to maximize client base.
- Market and promote through Social Media Marketing utilizing Facebook, Instagram, Canva, and Mail Chimp in order to increase brand awareness and client base to increase profit.
- Develop, plan, and carry-out customized training programs by leading up to 20 group classes and up to 35 individual sessions weekly to deliver expected client outcomes oftentimes exceeding client expectations.
- Nurture client relationships to build trust, morale in a fun and motivating way increasing client consistency, profit, client base, glowing reviews, and efficacy of programming.
- Learned a lot about human behavior change and learning.

Quality Assurance Tester

Epic Systems Corp, Verona, WI

2016-2017

• Create, implement, and track software testing plans to creatively find bugs, prevent problems, and escalate to the development team to meet the deadline of the system go-live and ensure excellent user experience.

Regan O'Brien Page 2

• Oversee, answer questions real time, and fill any knowledge gaps of hospital staff on-site at go-lives for the Anesthesia App while ensuring the seamless upgrade of the software in the fast-paced hospital environment.

Field Researcher

UW School of Medicine and Public Health, Madison, WI

2014-2015

- Gather, record and prepare data by conducting research interviews for submission to University in order to increase the overall health of Wisconsin's Dane County residents through knowledge acquisition.
- Work intimately with participants, maintaining the utmost scientific accuracy while ensuring confidentiality in order to stay HIPAA compliant.

PRIOR RELATED EXPERIENCE

Event Organizer Project Manager

"Elevated Movement" Fundraising Event Producer Madison WI

2019 - 2020

- Develop and execute an 8 month plan including risk management, task-delegation, and day-of coordination of volunteers, performers, vendors and attendees.
- Research and select venue, cast of performers, volunteers, host of event, and graphic designer based on reviews, fees, networking, and capabilities in order to compose a thrilling and profitable event.
- Promote the event via social media marketing, word-of-mouth, and advertising in well-trafficked community areas which resulted in a sold out 85 person venue and \$2,667 raised for the cause.

CCRC College Internship

Clark Lindsey Village, Urbana, IL

2013 - 2014

- Led activities with residents to enrich their day to day lives and I learned about the operations of a Continued Care Retirement Community.
- Applied what I was learning through my Community Health major in the implementation of the six dimensions of wellness.
- Collaborated with other student interns to create a schedule of activities and plan an activity fair for residents to choose events they'd like to participate in in the coming year.
- Learned a lot about human behavior and neurology

EDUCATION

UX/UI Bootcamp, Aug 2023-Feb2024 Northwestern University, Evanston, IL

Bachelor's of Science in Community Health, 2010-2014 University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign